{
    "subject": "resource/Roman_Catholic_Diocese_of_Honolulu",
    "predicate": "ontology/territory",
    "object": "resource/U.S._state",
    "human_readable": "The Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu is located in U.S. state.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887654781341553,
            "question": "In which U.S. state is the Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9835857152938843,
            "question": "Where is the Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8898208141326904,
            "question": "What type of organization is the Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8352921605110168,
            "question": "Does the Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu operate within a specific country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7449862957000732,
            "question": "How does the Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu contribute to the local community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5032234787940979,
            "question": "Could you name another diocese located in the U.S.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3356943428516388,
            "question": "Are there any other religious organizations present in Hawaii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23245084285736084,
            "question": "What is the primary function of a Roman Catholic Diocese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21510513126850128,
            "question": "What are some significant historical events related to the Roman Catholic Church in the U.S.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1302068531513214,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of dioceses found in different parts of the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu is located in U.S. state.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5517_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some significant historical events related to the Roman Catholic Church in the U.S.?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5517_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary function of a Roman Catholic Diocese?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5517_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other religious organizations present in Hawaii?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5517_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5517_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about the Diocese of Honolulu, stating it is for the state of Hawaii in the United States, which confirms that the Roman Catholic Diocese of Honolulu is indeed located in a U.S. state."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}